corehr.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy policy - CoreHR Site

This privacy policy sets out how CoreHR uses and protects any information that you give us or that we obtain about you from other sources

 **What personal information we collect**  
We collect contact detail, including name, email address and phone number  directly from you to to contact you in response to any requests you make for more information about our services or products.

​  
**How we use your personal information and why we believe that use is justified**  
Your personal information will be collected by CoreHR when you use the website.   The personal information we collect will only be used in the ways described below to meet our legitimate business interest in servicing and marketing to our Clients and prospective clients.  We only market to you if you have asked us to.

​At CoreHR we are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and only used in line with this Privacy Policy, which may be amended from time to time.

​The information we collect and hold on you, will be used by us and our subcontractors to:  
​  
·       provide you with any product or service you request;  
·       better understand your needs and improve our service to you;  
·       administrate any products or service we provide to you;  
·       profile and keep statistical records about you;  
·       conduct market research;  
·       communicate with you about our products & services, or other products and services we believe may be of interest to you.

 **Retention**  
​We only retain your data for as long as we have a business need to do. Your contact details are held while you have asked us for information or we are providing you with services and for a period of no longer than 7 years after we last did business with, or had contact with you.  We need to hold your information for this long to meet taxation obligations and to manage legal claims.  
​  
**Marketing**  
We may, where you have consented, periodically send promotional emails, letters or calls about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the contact information which you have provided.​

 **Security**  
​We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and organizational procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

 **Links to other websites**  
​Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

​ **How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website. We use cookies for statistical purposes such as tracking the pages you have visited, the frequency of your visits and your location. This, in turn, enables us to improve the way our website works. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. You may also choose to delete the cookies stored in your system any time. Our use of cookies is in accordance with applicable laws.

On this site we use Google Analytics cookies to check the statistics of people visiting our site.

 **For information on our Cookie policy, and how we process data, please see our policy here**
